<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<odoo>
    <record id="view_connect_add_credits_wizard_form" model="ir.ui.view">
        <field name="name">view_connect_add_credits_wizard_form</field>
        <field name="model">connect.add_credits_wizard</field>
        <field name="arch" type="xml">
            <form string="Add Credirs">
                <group>
                    <field name="formula" invisible="1"/>
                    <field name="pay_amount"/>
                    <field name="monthly_average" string="Your monthly average"/>
                    <field name="receive_amount"/>
                    <div colspan="2" class="o_form_label text-danger">Please check to confirm</div>
                    <field name="confirm_transaction"/>
                    <div colspan="2">
                        <h3>Add Credits to Balance: How It Works</h3>
                        <p>Our system offers bonuses when you add credits to your balance in advance. Here's how it works:</p>
                        <ol>
                            <li>
                                <strong>Monthly Fee Basis:</strong> Each credit top-up is calculated based on a standard monthly fee. When you pay in advance, the system automatically calculates the number of months covered by your payment.
                            </li>
                            <li>
                                <strong>Bonus for Multiple Months:</strong> The more months you pay for in advance, the higher the bonus you’ll receive. This means that, on top of the months you've paid for, you'll get extra credits as a thank-you for committing to a longer period.
                            </li>
                            <li>
                                <strong>Automatic Bonus Calculation:</strong> Our system applies a specific bonus multiplier to your payment based on the number of months covered. You don’t need to do any extra steps; the system will calculate and apply the bonus credits automatically.
                            </li>
                            <li>
                                <strong>Balance Update:</strong> Once your payment is processed, your balance will be updated with the total credits, including any bonuses, so you’ll see a higher amount in your account than what you paid for.
                            </li>
                        </ol>
                        <strong>This system allows you to maximize value by planning ahead. Enjoy added credits every time you commit to multiple months!</strong>
                    </div>
                </group>
                <footer>
                    <button string="Confirm" type="object" name="action_confirm" class="btn-primary"
                        confirm="Your credit card will be charged now. Please confirm."
                        invisible="confirm_transaction == False"/>
                    <button string="Cancel" class="btn-secondary" special="cancel"/>
                </footer>
            </form>
        </field>
    </record>

</odoo>
